No, no.
>> How do you think your your mom feels now
to know that Dan Quinn is a big fan of
you?
>> Uh, definitely ecstatic. I I believe she
is like just
happy, happy, happiest. Probably
happiest she's ever been, but um yeah,
it's very good. It's a blessing and uh
it's just unbelievable.
>> How do you think you'll be able to
contribute to these guys in year one?
>> Uh
really I set standards high for myself.
So like I believe I'll be able to make a
very dominant impact on that field and
just contribute to the success of our
team.
>> Where do you think your strength your
strength is on the field?
>> Um
I'm very I'm very boss savvy. I really
understand the game and I understand
concepts and
I watch a lot of film.
That's one of my biggest strengths. I
wouldn't say that's my biggest strength,
but
it's definitely up there if I can't
think off the top of my head what my
biggest strength would be, but
definitely that
>> you have a usually long wingspan. Um,
>> how much has that helped you? I mean,
that in other ways too is like it made
you a great basketball player or
something or
>> Yeah. Um, so
I mean that just helped me in general on
pass rush, run, uh, run defense, a whole
bunch of situations like that. But like
when it came to basketball, I was always
the lock down defender. Like if there
was a best player on the court and he
was giving us problems, like I stopped
playing basketball eighth grade, but up
to that point, if there was somebody on
the court giving us problem, I was the
person guarding him. So like it
definitely helped in basketball. But
really like when it comes to football,
my length is just like I I want to say
it's it's definitely one of my biggest
strengths, but I can't say it's my
biggest strength because like
the way I utilize it and the way I know
I can utilize it even more is just
crazy. So there's that.
>> Hey Josh, you should like this team even
more because there's a lot of hoopers on
this team. But what was the thing that
really stood out when you came here uh
that you liked about the command?
>> Um
how everybody was saying AP and and
Quinn like they they changed the culture
like they're they made it just like a
more player player type team. Like
everything they do from the is for the
players. Even like when the strength
coach was giving me a tour of the
facility and giving me breakdowns about
the things that was just added and the
things they plan to add because players
are asking for these things is just
that's what really stood out for me.
>> You guys played against I think LSU and
Jaden Daniels your freshman year. What
what do you remember about that?
>> Uh shout out him. I got my first
collegiate sack on him. So that was that
game when I happened and I remember we
put belt to Yeah. So like
But that game, yeah, that game was just
one because it was my first like
collegiate sack and I had a couple
pressures on him on top of that. So,
>> what do you remember about the sack?
What what what happened on the play?
>> Uh, we had like a tech stunt. So, the
three tech next to me, he stabbed the
gap. I just ran up and under and I
basically came free. By the time the
guard tried to reach out for me, I just
dipped under his shoulder. Excuse me.
And then like I was like head up with
him and he tried to side step. So I end
up grabbing him, tagged on him. That's
it.
>> Did you say anything to him?
>> Nah, I was like too ecstatic. Like I got
up like
>> just like, you know what I'm saying?
Flexing and stuff cuz it was really
surprisingly I think that was my first
play in that game
>> and I think it was like a Yeah, it was
the first play of the drive and it just
it happened onto my lap.
>> All right. Appreciate it.
>> Congratulations. Congrats.
>> All right. I appreciate y'all, man. God
bless y'all, man. Have a good day.
>> Thank you.